humaniplex.com 2011-09-02

# HX - Humaniplex.com Privacy Policy

### Humaniplex.com Privacy Policy

Last Modified: June 05, 2010

Humaniplex.com recognizes that your privacy is important and is committed to protecting it. This Privacy Policy applies to all products and services provided by Humaniplex.com.

#### What Information is Collected

When you browse the world wide web, you are connecting your computer with other computers. This method of communication requires that you make a request to a remote computer or remote system of computers (often called a "server"), and then you receive an answer back with information. To properly get the information you requested back to you, your computer needs to send your Internet Protocol address (or IP address) to the remote computer, which uses it to return data. This is root premise of the Internet.

  * **Basic Internet Information** \- When you access any website, some information such as your web request, IP address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and potentially some cookies (a small file containing a string of characters) are recorded by the receiving system.

Humaniplex.com is no different. When you access this site, our servers record the information your browser sends to it so that it can properly send back the pages you requested.

  * **Cookies** \- Cookies are used by Humaniplex.com to remember some of your preferences and personalization choices, but mainly to remember that you are logged in. Cookies are not used to track your usage trends or to generate an advertising profile for you.
  * **Information You Provide To Us** \- When you sign up for Humaniplex.com you provide us with your email address, gender, and birth date. Your gender and age (not your direct birth date) are publicly displayed on the site. Your email address (and your password recovery email address) are never displayed to anyone but you, nor shared, sold, rented to any third party.
  * **Information You Publish** \- This is the Internet Age. With the positives come the negatives. When you send a letter to someone, you essentially lose control of that letter. The recipient can take your letter and show countless people. The same with a photo. Once you publish a photo, anyone who sees it can reuse it and rebroadcast it over and over again. With the Internet, this process of non-consentual information sharing has become extremely accelerated. Copyright issues and legality aside, right or wrong, it happens, and there is nothing you can do to prevent it if you share information on the Internet.

Humaniplex.com is no different. As you use this site and participate by publishing blogs, uploading photos, and using the features and services provided to you, you will be sharing content with people you know, and a lot of people you don't know. Once you publish anything on this site, or any other website, you have no idea where it might end up. If you do not want to share content, you do not have to. But if you do, your content is out there forever outside of your control and Humaniplex.com's control. Additionally, Humaniplex.com will not remove content which you yourself have explicitly already published (unless it is in violation of the Terms of Service), as that creates a complete lack of accountability for your actions and words.

In addition, search engines such as Google basically crawl every single page on the web for data to add to their databases. Anything you publish in a public place or that is displayed on your profile can be indexed and displayed as search results there. Therefore, you should never post any information on this or any other social networking site that you would not want to become public information.

Remember, only you can control what you choose to share about yourself. Humaniplex.com does not force you to share anything except a name you make up for yourself, your gender, and your age. The rest is up to you.

  * **Information About You From Other Users** \- The disclosure of personal contact information as related to you as a human being is a violation of the Terms of Service of this site. You may choose to publish or disclose your real name, phone number, address, etc (even though it is not recommended to do so), however, unless you have already done so, others may not.

However, as a user, your identity is your handle (or screen name, or site name). Your alter ego. Discussion about your actions or words in the context of your handle can and will occur. This is not a privacy issue.

Besides people privately or publicly having discussion about you, people can use the Humaniplex.com Network to rate you. You have no control over these ratings, as they are generated by other people from their accounts. Ratings are not removed by Humaniplex.com under any circumstances. You may receive ratings that are either undeserved or that you simply feel are undeserved. People being people, it happens frequently. This is also not a privacy issue.

  * **Completely Public Information** \- Includes, but is not limited to:  

    * Your handle, gender, and age
    * Humaniplex.com specific information, such as:  

      * Some of your ratings
      * Statistics about your blogging
      * Photos you choose to be viewable to "everyone"

#### How We Use Your Information

  * **To Provide The Service** \- We use the information we collect to provide our services and features to you, to measure and improve those services and features, and to provide you with customer support. We use the information to prevent potentially illegal activities, and to enforce our Terms of Service. We also use a variety of technological systems to detect and address anomalous activity and screen content to prevent abuse such as spam. These efforts may on occasion result in a temporary or permanent suspension or termination of some functions for some users.
  * **To Contact You** \- We may contact you with service-related announcements from time to time. You may opt out of all communications except essential updates on your account settings page.

#### How We Share Your Information

  * **When You Make a Purchase** \- The information you provide to us is not provided to our credit card processors. You will need to seperately provide them with some personal information that is necessary, for example, to charge your credit card. Our systems need to send our processors some information to make the application of FXPoints and account releases function correctly. However, it is exchanged in an encrypted format. In other words, our payment processors will ask you directly for the information they need for you to make a payment, but do not receive any of your Humaniplex.com account information from us. 
  * **To Provide Our Affiliates with Social Networking Services** \- Our affiliates never receive any personal information about you, not even your email address. To provide our Social Networking Services, Humaniplex.com shares some basic information associated with your account with our affiliates so that they can better provide you with personalized services. This information includes:  

    * Your account handle
    * Aggregate information about ratings. This is provided so that our affiliates can choose to apply their algorithms to our network ratings data about your to generate their own system of labeling.
The data about your account that is provided to our affiliates includes no personally identifiable information, and no method of contact outside of Humaniplex.com. So they are unable to spam you, even if they wanted to. 
  * **To Respond to Legal Requests and Prevent Harm** \- If we have a good faith belief that the response is required by law, we may disclose information pursuant to subpoenas, court orders, or other requests (including criminal and civil matters). This may include honoring requests from jurisdictions outside of the United States where we have a good faith belief that the response is required by law under the local laws in that jurisdiction, apply to users from that jurisdiction, and are consistent with generally accepted international standards. We may also share information when we have a good faith belief it is necessary to prevent fraud or other illegal activity, to prevent imminent bodily harm, or to protect ourselves and you from people violating our Terms of Service. This may include sharing information with lawyers, courts or other government entities. 
  * **Your Information Is NEVER Used for Marketing, Promotion, or Advertising by Third Parties!** \- We do not sell or lease personal information. Many websites, specifically socials networks such as this one, choose to sell their users' personal information to third parties so that those third parties can advertise to you. Worse yet, many sites profile your browsing habits to try to generate a picture on the things you might buy and then sell that information to third parties.

That is not the case here, and never will be.
